（男鹿）((ベル坊は人間を
滅ぼしたりしね～よ→
Baby Beel ain't gonna destroy the Human World...
なんで　わかるかって？
オレが親だからだ))
How do I know, you ask?
Because I'm the parent!
（ヒルダ）((あっ…))
((ベル坊～。いない
いない　ばぁ～→
Baby Beel!
Peek a boo!
パパでちゅよ～？))
（ベル坊）((ダ～ブ～))
It's Daddy!
((ダァ～！フフッ…))
((ベル坊～　パパと　この金髪
どっちが好きかな？))
Baby Beel... Who do you like better, Dad or this blond?
((ダベシ！))
((うっ！？…あっ))
((そ～か　そ～だよなぁ。
考えてみりゃ→
Yeah! Definitely.
殴ることしか取り柄がない
メイド女なんて→
When you think about it,
some maid who can't do anything more than punch isn't fit to raise a child.
子育て上　よくないよな～))
((アイ　ダブ～))
よ～し　親子水入らずで
遊園地でも行くか))
((ダブ～！))
Okay! Let's head to an amusement park as father and son, without anyone else butting it!
((くぅ…！ぼ…坊っちゃま！→
M-Master!
坊っちゃま～～！→
Master!
あっ…坊っちゃま～…))
坊っちゃま～！！…あっ！？
Master!
あっ…。
ふぅ…。ゆ…夢か。
A-A dream?
縁起でもない。
坊っちゃまが私より→
This couldn't be a premonition...
There's no way the Master would love that sewer-rat more than...
あのドブ男の方が好きなどと…。
あ～　やめろ。ベル坊！
んっ！？
（美咲）アッハハ…仲良いわね～。
Stop it, Baby Beel!
ダブダブ　ダブ～…。
うがぁ　ぐがぁ…。
You two sure get along.
ダブィ～！
ぐあぁ～っ！！
アッハハハ…。
笑ってね～で　止めろよ！
Don't stand there laughing! Stop him!
親子水入らずのとこ
お邪魔しました～！
I wouldn't want to butt in between father and son.
うぐっ　うぐっ！
うっ…。
おっ　ちょうど良かった。
おい　お前も止め…。
Oh, perfect... Would you please stop–
えい！
（ガシャン！）
あっ…ああ～…。
貴様　あまり調子に乗るなよ！→
You bastard! Don't get such a big head!
坊っちゃまを独り占めする気か！
ああ！？
You plan on having the Master all to yourself?!
長いこと名前も出ていないから
忘れておるかもしれんがな…→
His name hasn't shown up in a while, so maybe you've forgotten...
貴様はベヘモット３４柱師団から
狙われているのだぞ！→
But you're being targeted by Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division!
私ぬきで　あやつらに
対抗できると思っておるのか！
You think you can oppose them without me, do you?!
何　わけわかんね～こと
言ってんだ！？→
What are you blabbing about? And why did you punch me all of a sudden?
いきなり　殴りやがって！
あっ！
それしか…。
んっ？
Are you...
それしか　取り柄がないとでも
言うつもりか～！！
Are you saying that's all I'm good at?!
はぁあ！？
ぐぁあ～～！！
（爆発音）
貴様の子育ての何がわかる！
What do you know about raising a child?!
ぐぁあ～～！！
（爆発音）
おい！？お前　なに言って…。
Hey! What are you...
ぐはぁ～！！
（爆発音）
（母）辰巳！遅刻するわよ～。
Tatsumi, you're going to be late.
何なんだ　バカヤロー！
今日は急いでっから→
What's wrong with you, idiot?!
このぐらいにしといてやら～！
この…バ～カ！バ～カ！
I'm in a hurry today, so we'll settle this later!
You stupid idiot!
フン…。んっ！？
また　坊っちゃまのミルクを…。
まったく→
He forgot the Master's milk again...
だから　あの男は親としての
自覚が足りないというのだ。
Honestly... That's exactly why that man has no business being a parent.
あれ？
辰巳　もう行っちゃった？
Oh? Did Tatsumi leave already?
どうかしたのですか？
Is something the matter?
ん～…。さっき
聞くの忘れてたんだけどさ→
I forgot to ask him before...
ホントなのかね～？もうすぐ→
I've heard that Ishiyama's new school building was almost finished being built.
石矢魔の新校舎が建つって噂。
石矢魔の新校舎…ですか？
Ishiyama's new school building?
Ishiyama High School
（ベヘモット）フッ…。
Akumano Academy is Open
（不良）うわっは～！石矢魔～
ふっかぁぁ～つ！
Oh, yeah! Ishiyama is baaaack!
（不良）≪ついに　この時が…≫
（不良達）バンザ～イ！
It's finally time!
（不良）≪オレ達の学園が
帰ってくるぞ～≫
（不良達）バンザ～イ！
Our paradise has returned!
（神崎）
やれやれ…。うちの野郎どもは
アホばっかりだぜ。
Man, our students are all idiots.
そんなこと言って
（夏目）
まざりたいんでしょ？
You say that, but I bet you wanna join in.
バ～カ　オレは
そこまでガキじゃね～よ。
Fool. I'm not some little kid.
よ～し！誰が
（不良）
一番に落書きするか→
Okay! Let's play rock-paper-scissors to decide who gets to graffiti first!
ジャンケンしよ～ぜ！
ああっ！？オレに決まってんだろ。
Huh?! Me, obviously!
（不良）≪い～や　オレだ！≫
（不良）≪冗談じゃねぇよ　おい！≫
（神崎）バカヤロウ！→
Idiots! That's obviously a job for the head-honcho of Ishiyama... Me, Kanzaki-san!
そいつは石矢魔のトップ
神崎さんの仕事だろうが！！
（不良）≪あ～　ずるいっスよ
神崎さん！≫
Aw, that's not fair, Kanzaki-san!
（神崎）１人１回　８文字までだ！→
Each of you can write 8 letters at a time, max!
ガラス割りも
マナーを守って１人１枚！
And obey proper manners by only breaking one window, each!
≪うんこマークは
１文字に入るんスか？≫
Does a picture of poop count as a letter?
（神崎）
ダメだ！幼稚すぎるかならな！
Not allowed! That's too immature!
（寧々）ガキ…。
Brats...
（由加）でも　確かに
楽しみじゃないっスか？
But, aren't you looking forward to it?
んん～…。楽しみは楽しみだけど
石矢魔が壊れてから→
Well, sure, but it's only been 3 months since Ishiyama was destroyed...
３ヶ月ぐらいしか
経ってないでしょう？→
そんな早く建設できるもんなの？
みょ～にデカイし…。
Can they really rebuild it that fast?
And it's... strangely big.
（千秋）姫川先輩が
何か関わってるとか？
Did Himekawa-senpai have a hand in it?
（姫川）あん？知らね～よ。→
Don't ask me.
んなもんに　金出すくらいだったら
マンション建てるわ。
If I'm gonna pay that kind of money I'd build an apartment building.
なんか胡散臭いのよね～。
There's definitely something fishy going on.
（生徒）誰だ？あのじいさん。
Who's that old man?
（生徒）さあ。新しい先生とか？
Who knows? Maybe a new teacher?
（生徒達）んっ！？
お前さんら　ちと尋ねるが→
Pardon me for asking, but do you know where Ishiyama's classroom is?
石矢魔の教室というのは
どこかの？
（生徒）い…石矢魔！？
（生徒）
関わらない方がいいっすよ！
I-Ishiyama?!
You're better off not bothering them...
質問に答えんかい。
Will you answer me, or not?
（２人）えっ！！
男鹿辰巳という男を捜している。
どこじゃ？
I am searching for a man named Oga Tatsumi.
Where is he?
んっ？
ニョ？
ほぉ…背中に赤ん坊。
貴様がそうか？
Ah, with a baby on his back...
Seems like you're the one.
違います！
（ベヘモット）えっ！？
Uh, no.
全然　違います！
いやいや…→
Not at all.
男鹿辰巳じゃろう？
こらっ　待たんか！
You're Oga Tatsumi, right?
Hey, wait!
完璧　違いまぁ～す！
Definitely not me!
こらぁ～～！！
Hey!
（神崎）よ～し　野郎ども！→
Okay, punks!
新しい校舎を見に行くぞ～！
（不良達）おお～っ！
Let's go check out the new school building!
（佐渡原）いや…あの～神崎君…→
Yes, well, Kanzaki-kun... It's time to start homeroom...
今からホームルーム
…っていうか　そこ教卓…。
And, that's my desk!
だが　しかし！
仁義を欠いちゃならねぇ！
However, we can't neglect proper etiquette!
全員　佐渡原に注目！→
Everyone, look at Sadohara!
今まで　お世話になりました！
（不良達）お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for everything until now!
Thank you very much!
呼び捨て…これから
ホームルームだったんだけどね。
They didn't even call me "sensei"...
And I'm supposed to start homeroom now...
んっ…？→
君は行かないのかい？
あん？
You're not going?
Huh? Don't be stupid.
バカ言ってんじゃね～よ。
んっ…えっ！？
（ヘリコプターの音）
（蓮井）竜也坊っちゃま～！
お迎えに上がりました～！
Master Tatsuya!
I've come to pick you up!
オレ　ヘリで行くから。
ハッハハ…。
I'm going by helicopter!
もう　好きにして！
Suit yourselves!
ん…。
《大体…あの男は　なぜ　あの時
あんな事を言ったのだ？→
Why did he say that back then in the first place?
魔界すべてを敵に
まわすようなことを…》
Making an enemy of the entire Demon World...
《親としては　まだまだ
未熟であるというのに…》
As a parent he still has so much left to learn, and yet...
おっ…。
Fujino Meats
Fist Croquette!!
（チャイム）
え～っと…。
おら！ベル坊　飯だ。
ダブ！
Here, Baby Beel. Lunch.
それにしても　何なんだ
さっきの　じじい？
But, what was with that old man before?
いきなり　追っかけてきやがって。
Chasing after me all of a sudden like that...
（グゥ～！）
あっ！
オレの飯。うわっ！
やべ…家に忘れてきたか？
Gotta eat myself.
Crap, I forgot it at home!
おい！
んっ？
ニョ？
Hey.
ヒルダ？
何してんだ　お前？
Hilda!
What are you doing here?
おお～。わり～わり～…んっ！？
Oh, sorry about that...
そういや珍しいな…
お前がオレの弁当を届けるなんて。
That's strange... You brought me my lunch?
フン！感謝して敬え。→
Be grateful.
ついでだから
デザートもつけてやった。
I even put in some dessert for you.
ん…？デザート？
Dessert?
フフッ…。
（ヒュウ～！）
んっ！？
フッ！
うわっ！
ニョ！？
やれやれ　見失ってしもうたわ。
My, oh my... I lost site of him.
聞いてた以上に
ひねくれたガキじゃわい。
He's a more slippery brat than I'd heard.
何しやが…フガッフガッ…！
あいつは…。
What the hell are you doing?!
That's...
（早乙女）そろそろ　誰か来る頃だと思ってたが…→
I figured someone'd be coming sooner or later...
まさか　てめえが来るとはな。
By I never thought it'd be you.
（石動校長）うむ…。
（葵の祖父）うむ…。
（ベヘモット）
早乙女殿か…あんたが絡んで
おったとは…なるほどな→
Saotome-dono, is that you?
So, you're involved... I see now.
こりゃあ…わし　ピンチかの？
Maybe I'm in a little bit of trouble?
ぬかせ。余裕満々で敵状視察
しやがって。
Get off it...
After waltzing in here at ease to spy on the enemy...
（ベヘモット）いやいや。今日は挨拶に
来ただけじゃ。→
Now, now... I just came today to greet you.
そっちの２人とも久しい間柄での。
Me and those two go way back, you see.
ちと　老けたな…
石動源磨。邦枝一刀斎。
You've aged a bit, Isurugi Genma, Kunieda Ittousai.
お前に言われたくない。
St. Ishiyama Headmaster - Isurugi Genma
I don't want to hear that from you.
十数年ぶりか。
Shingetsu School Master - Kunieda Ittousai
How many decades has it been?
（校長）挨拶と言ったの。
ふっ…うう～ん！！→
You said you came to greet us?
ならば　わしからも！
Then, I'll go first!
何の漫画のキャラじゃい。
What kind of manga character is this?
ウウ～…ダャ～！
（衝撃波）
ううっ…ああ…。
（一同）うわ～～っ！
ま…間近で見ると
マジパネェっスね…。
Seeing it up close, it's totally crazy!
やっぱ　姫ちゃんが
関わってるんじゃないの？
Are we sure that Hime-chan didn't have a hand in this?
すごすぎるよ　これ…。
It's just way too much...
フッ！
関係ね～な。誰がつくろうと→
Like it matters.
No matter who made it, it's mine starting now!
今日から　こいつは
オレ様のもんだ！シューツと…。
With a spritz!
（不良）あっ　ずるいっスよ！
神崎さん！
That's not fair, Kanzaki-san!
（不良）
落書き順は　さっきババ抜きで
決めたじゃないっスか！
We decided on who got to graffiti first with that card game before!
（不良）ドベッすよ。神崎さんは！
（神崎）うるせ～　はなせ！→
No fair, Kanzaki-san!
Shut up, let me go!
オレは　ここに
「神崎さんの」って書くんだよ～！
I'm going to write "Property of Kanzaki-san"!
（業者）は～い　ごめんね。君たち。
（神崎・不良達）んっ！？
Hey, pardon us!
（業者）ちょっと　どいてて下さい。
Can you move aside for a bit?
（業者）外れるか？
（業者）
おっ…結構しっかり着いてるな。
Can we take it off?
It's stuck on pretty good.
あ…あの何を？
Um, what are you...
（業者）看板の取り外しですけど？
We're replacing the sign, and...?
取り外しって…何で？ここは
石矢魔高校の新校舎でしょ？
Replacing it?
Why? This is Ishiyama High School's new building, right?
あれ…聞いてないんですか？→
Huh? You didn't hear?
別の学校に
変わるらしいですよ…ここ。
This place is changing to a different school.
（生徒達）なっ！？
（業者）ほら　これが新しい看板。
See? This is the new sign.
（祖父）心月流…　。
Shigetsu Sword School Style Eighth Style: Kannagi.
（爆発音）
せっかちな　じじいどもが！
挨拶だけと言うとろうが…。
Hasty old men.
I thought I told you I was just here for a greeting!
避けたか…。
Dodged it, did he?
（早乙女）挨拶？
（ベヘモット）んっ！？
Greeting?
（早乙女）そいつは　つまり…→
In other words...
そいつは　つまり　宣戦布告って
ことだよな…ベヘモット。
In other words, you're here for a declaration of war, aren't you, Behemoth?
ついに　来たか…。
He finally came...
おい…何が！？
静かにしろ！
Hey! What's come?
Stay quiet!
あの　ケタ違いの魔力が
わからんのか！
Can't you feel that incredible Demon power?
（ベヘモット）宣戦布告？
違うと言うとるじゃろ。→
Declaration of war?
That's not what I said at all!
挨拶じゃよ…お隣さんに。
（校長）えっ！？
I've come to greet you!
As a good neighbor.
フッ。学校を作った。→
I made a school.
焔王坊っちゃまのための
学校をじゃ。
A school for Lord En.
なっ…。
坊っちゃまには　いろいろ
学んでもらわねばならんでのう。→
There's quite a lot that the Master needs to learn, see.
まあ　これから…
いろいろ　よろしくの～。
Well, I'm sure we'll be dealing with each other a lot from now on.
（生徒達）な…なにぃ～～！？
Akumano Academy
W-What?!
（ざわめき）
Huh? What's everyone doing here?
（古市）あれ？どうしたんすか
みんな　そろって。
おう古市。
やつら　とうとう来たぞ。
やつら？
Oh, Furuichi...
They're finally here.
They?
Akumano Academy.
悪魔野学園だ。
いやいや　何言ってんすか。
あれはオレが適当…。
What are you saying?
That's just something I came up wi...
マジでか…。
It's freakin' huge!
（邦枝）ちょっと
待ちなさいってば！
I told you to wait.
I can smell a seriously powerful Demon!
（コマちゃん）ものごっつい悪魔の匂いがすんねん！
You've been saying that since this morning.
今朝からそればっかりで
ちっとも見当たらないじゃない。
But we haven't seen head or tail of it!
I'm tellin' you it's the truth this time!
今度こそホンマやって！→
なんか匂いを隠してたもんが
なくなったみたいや。
It hid its scent or something and disappeared.
葵ちゃん。気ぃ引き締めや。→
Aoi-chan, stay on guard.
This ain't the smell of your average Demon.
この匂い　並みの悪魔やないで。
（チャイム）
Stand, bow, take your seats.
≪きり～つ　れ～い　ちゃくせき≫
（高橋）え～皆さん　はじめまして。
本日付で　この学校に→
Um, how do you do everyone?
My name is Takahashi, and I am going to be your teacher here at this... school...
赴任いたしました
私　高橋ともうします。
《なんだ　このクラス
高校だよね？ここ》
What's with this class?
This is a high school, right?
U-Um, let's take attendance.
え　え～　では出席をとりましょう。バジリスク君でいいのかな？
Basilisk-kun... Are you here?
（バジリスク）は～い！
Yes!
《え！バジリスク君？
おっさんじゃん！→
Basilisk-kun?! He's a grown man!
He's smoking a cigar!
葉巻じゃん！エラあるじゃん！》
And he's got gills!
フ～…先生。わしら人間界の事は→
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar Master
Basilisk
Teacher, I don't know a thing about the Human World.
なんも知らんのですわ。
I look forward to your guidance and instruction.
ご鞭撻の程
よろしくお願いします。→
人間滅ぼすには　まず人間の事を
よく知らねばいかんですからな。→
Before destroying the Humans, we must learn all we can about them, after all!
ガハハハ…！
はあ　そうですか。
Oh, is that so?
I don't know what in the world he's talking about.
《何言ってっか
さっぱりわかんない。→
え？何を滅ぼすって？》
You're going to destroy what?
（アギエル）
おう　おっさん
笑ってないで座んなよ。→
Hey pops, don't stand there laughing and take a seat.
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar General
Agiel
後がつかえてんだからさ～。
I wanna get this over with.
アギエル…
相変わらずクソ生意気な娘だ。→
Agiel...
Just as uppity a little girl as ever.
Know your place as a Pillar General.
柱将の分際で。
お？なんだ　やんのか？ゴリラ！
Oh, what was that?
You wanna go, gorilla?
Now, now you two...
（サラマンダー）
まあまあ　２人とも
アギエルちゃんもダメだよ→
Agiel-chan, you should do that.
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar Master
Salamander
目上の人に
そんな口きいちゃ。
You mustn't talk to your superiors like that.
あの　すいませんが…。
ああ　どうも失礼→
Um, excuse me...?
Oh, pardon me.
Please continue, Teacher.
続けてください。先生。
《も　問題の多いクラスなのかな
今のアギエルって子も→
Does this class have a lot of problem children?
That Agiel girl... She's wearing a bikini under her coat.
コートの中　ビキニだし》
I think it's best I don't say too much...
《あまり　つっこまない方がよさそうだな》
Um... Quetzalcoatl-kun!
え～っと　ケツァルコアトル君。
（ケツァルコアトル）あ　は～い。
H-Here!
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar Master
Quetzalcoatl
《う…ピエロやん！》
He's a clown!
Q-Quetzalcoatl-kun... It says here you're a "Pillar Master"?
ケ　ケツァルコアトル君は
ここに　柱爵とありますが？
Oh, yes.
（ケツァルコアトル）ああ　ええ。
（高橋）なにこれ？
What's that?
柱爵ですね。
A Pillar Master.
《だから　なんなんだよ～！
それはあぁ～！》
And what is that?!
It seems the teacher does not know what a Pillar Master is.
（夜刀）先生は柱爵が
分かっておられない様子。
Someone should explain it to him.
ここは　誰か説明した方が
よろしいのでは？
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar Master
Yato
（高橋）《お前はまず　刀を持ってる理由を説明しろぉ～！→
First, explain why you have a katana on your back!
バカヤロウ！》
Idiot!
（オドネル）では　僭越ながら私が。
ヘッ？
Then, shall I?
First, Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division is...
（オドネル）そもそも
ベヘモット３４柱師団とは…。
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar General
Odonel
Why are you all tied up?!
《なんで　あっちこっち縛られ
てんの～　君は！お母さ～ん！》
Mommy!
...organized into 24 Pillar Generals and 10 Pillar Masters.
２４名の柱将と　１０名の柱爵が
指揮を務める組織です。→
The Pillar Masters are each given the names of famous dragons.
柱爵にはそれぞれ　由緒ある
ドラゴンの名が与えられています。
《なんだこのクラスは
まともな子がいないじゃないか→
What's with this class?
There's not a normal student in the bunch!
最近の若い子は
どうなっちゃってるんだ》
What's wrong with kids these days?
Each Pillar Master has 2 or 3 Pillar Generals that serve them.
（オドネル）柱爵は２名ないし３名の
柱将を部下にもちます。
No, no... I've finally found a new job, so...
《い　いや　せっかく見つけた
再就職先だ。→
I've got to make my stand here, or Mother will...
ここで踏ん張らないと母ちゃんに…》
Thank you! I understand.
あ　ありがとね。
よくわかりましたよ→
では続けましょう。
はい　えっと…焔王君！
Well, let me continue.
Right... Lord En-kun!
Huh? Lord En-kun!
あれ？焔王く～ん！
おいメガネ！焔王「君」だと！？
はい？
Hey, specs!
Did you just say Lord En-kun?!
That's Lord En-sama to you, buddy!
焔王「様」だろうが～！
次　そんなナメた呼び方したら→
The next time you address him like that, we'll kill you!
ぶっ殺すぞ　おらぁ～！
え　え　え　焔王様ぁ～！
Lord En-sama!
Here!
（焔王）は～い！
《えっ？あっ　こど…も…だ》
A... kid...
《なに？このクラス。ハハハ…》
What's with this class?
む？倒れられたな。
He's fainted.
Huh? What a wimp.
なになに？軟弱だなぁ。
（鐘の音）
ふむ…。
Have some rats snuck in?
（アギエル）
ネズミが入りこんだかな～？
（神崎）ど　どうするよ。
W-What'll we do?
We can't just go home now.
（夏目）このまま帰るわけにも
いかないでしょ。
（由加）のりこみますか！
Should we sneak in?!
ええ！？いやいや花澤さん
それはさすがに　まずいっすよ！
No, no, Hanazawa-san... That's really not a good idea.
《冗談じゃねぇぞ。このメンバーでもし悪魔たちに出くわしたら→
You've gotta be kidding me!
If we encounter some Demons with this group, we'll be dead-meat for real!
ガチで即死だ！》
（姫川）おう　お前ら
こっちだ　こっち。→
Hey, people.
This way.
昇降口　カギ開いてんぞ。
見てみろよ。→
The entrance over here is unlocked.
Take a look. This place is decked out beyond belief.
想像以上にいかれてやがるぜ。悪魔野学園。
Akumano Academy...
That brat... What is he, seriously?
（神崎）あのガキ　マジで何者だよ→
This is way beyond some ringleader...
ただの首謀者とかいう
レベルじゃねぇぞ　これ。
Maybe he plans on being a god or something.
（夏目）神様にでも
なったつもりかね。
I researched online but nothing showed up.
ネットで検索かけても
何も出てこねぇ。
マジで得体のしれねえ学校だ。→
I've got no idea who's behind this school.
I thought I would check out the inside while there wasn't anyone here.
人の気配がねぇうちに　中を
見てやろうと思ってな。ここだ。
This is it.
や　やめましょうよ。勝手に
入ったりしたら怒られますよ！
Let's not! They might get angry if we just barge in...
ああ？何言ってんだ。
もともとオレらの校舎だろうが。
Hey, what are you saying?
This was our school building to begin with!
Yeah, that's right! No holding back!
そうそう。遠慮は無用っすよ！
This is kinda like a haunted house! I'm all excited!
なんか　ちょっとお化け屋敷
みたいでドキドキするっすね。
うん。
おお～　中もすげぇな。
The inside's amazing, too.
天井　たっか！
High ceiling!
（扉の閉まる音）
あっ…え！？
今　あの扉　勝手に
閉まらなかったっすか？
Did that door just close on its own?
Huh? It was just the wind, right?
はぁ？風だろ？
由加！いい加減にしなさいよ！
Yuka, cut it out!
（神崎達の足音）
Sheesh... Why aren't there any lights on?
もぅ　なんで電気の
ひとつもついてないのよ。
寧々さん　怖いんすか？
Nene-san, you scared?
そ　そういうわけじゃないけど！
N-Not at all!
おい　おかしくねぇか。→
Hey, this is strange.
ここまで歩いて
上にあがる階段が見当たらねぇ。
We've walked a while but haven't seen any stairs leading up.
そういえば…。
やっぱ危険っすよ！
Now that you mention it...
I knew this was dangerous!
帰りましょう！
今すぐにダッシュで！
Let's go home! Right now! On the double!
そういや　オレも
気になってたんだけどよ…。
Actually, I've been worried about something as well.
（神崎）あ？
（寧々）なによ？
（古市）無視っすか！？ガン無視！？
What?
Ignoring me? Completely?
人数　増えてねえか？
（夏目・城山）あ？
Don't we have a couple... extra people?
えっ！？
ハッ！
Oh, you noticed?
ありゃ　気付かれたか。
I'm Agiel-chan! A Pillar General of Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division!
ベヘモット３４柱師団柱将
アギエルちゃんだよ。
（神崎・姫川）はぁ？
And I am also a Pillar General, Odonel.
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar General (Once Again)
Odonel
同じく柱将　オドネル。
柱将　ゼラ。
Pillar General, Zela.
Behemoth's 34 Pillar Division - Pillar General
Zela
W-What are these guy's saying?
な　なに言ってんだ　こいつら。
《っていうか　すごい格好だな》
And whoa, what a crazy getup!
ふ～ん　君たちだよねぇ
ヘカちゃんとグラちゃん→
You're the guys on Beelze-sama's side who beat up Heca-chan and Gra-chan...
フルボッコにした
ベルゼ様の家臣って。
な～んか弱そ。
Man, you look weak.
We've been with you this whole time and you never noticed.
さっきからずっと一緒にいたのに
気づかないんだもん。
あんた達こそ　その服
悪魔野学園の生徒ね？
And you, with that outfit! You're a student of Akumano Academy, aren't you?
What's the meaning of this?
どういうことよ　これ！
プッフフフ…。
なによ？
Yup, Akumano Academy!
そうそう。悪魔野学園ね。
坊っちゃまのネーミングセンスにも→
Can't help the Master's naming sense, I'm afraid...
困ったもんだよね～。
ウフフフ…アハハハ…。
《なんだ　こいつ》
Who are these guys?
Hey, girly!
（不良）おいこら　ね～ちゃんよ。
（不良）
ナメてんじゃね～ぞ
なんだ　そのふざけた格好は？
You lookin' down on us?
What's with the freaky getup?
アハハ！なんだなんだ？→
Well, look what the cat dragged in!
むさくるしいなぁ。
え？
うおっ！うおっ！
（３人）あ　ああ…。
言い忘れてたけど進入禁止だよ。
Maybe I forgot to mention this...
...but trespassing is forbidden.
このっ！
お？
Why, you...!
Nene-san, awesome!
寧々さん　さすが！
捕まえたわよ。
I was ready!
オドネル　お揃い！
I'm matching Odonel!
Get on with it.
いいから。
わかってるって。
All right, all right...
The Division is still halted...
団長には
まだ止められてるんだけど…。
１人２人ぐらい
殺してもいいよね！
But I'm sure it won't matter if I kill one or two!
おおお…おっ。
間一髪　間に合ったわね。
In the nick of time...
I made it.
Madame Aoi!
葵姐さん！
Who are you?
何だ？お前。→
I thought we made it so no one else could get in.
もう人は入れないように
しといたはずだけど…。
もう一度確認するけど→
Let me double check something...
You definitely can't be seen by normal people, right?
本当に普通の人には
見えないんでしょうね。
Exactly!
（コマちゃん）当然や。葵ちゃんかて
最初は見えへんかったやろ。
You couldn't see me at first either, remember?
Got it.
わかったわ…寧々。
Nene!
はい。
下がってって。
巻きこまれないようにね。
Yes?
Stand back. Far enough not to get in the way.
What's this?
なんだなんだ？お嬢ちゃん１人で
相手するつもりかい？
You plan on taking me on yourself?
（コマちゃん）
葵ちゃん　あの真ん中のメガネっ娘ええなぁ。エロいなぁ。エ～ヘヘ！
Aoi-chan...
That glasses girl in the middle's pretty sexy, huh?
Yeah. I thought you'd say that, so shut up.
（邦枝）うん。言うと
思ってたけど黙ってて。
（コマちゃん）攻撃したはずみに
ポロリとかあっても→
After we attack maybe her boobs'll pop out!
しゃあないんちゃうか！？
黙れっての　エロ犬。
（邦枝）
I said shut up, you pervy dog.
なにか…いるぞ。
There's something here...
（邦枝）準備はいい？
Are you ready?
最初から全力で行くわよ。
We're going all out from the start!
Calm down, Baby Beel!
Next up, we're gonna finish this with our cool Super Milk Time!
You okay, Oga?
It looks like they've even got a giant dragon with them!
On the next Beelzebub:
We're the Strongest!
Strongest? You mean, me?
Baby Beel... When this battle is over, let's eat fist croquettes together!
Sorry about trying to lighten things up...